http://www.scripttoscreen.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
We respect your privacy rights and recognize the importance of protecting data collected from you and about you. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) describes how we collect, use, share, and protect that data. Your use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
Collection of Personal Data
We do not collect information that identifies you personally when you visit our website, unless you voluntarily provide it. When you browse the Script to Screen website, you do so anonymously without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. You are free to browse our site without entering any personal information and therefore remain anonymous during your visit.
General Information Collection
Although we do not collect personal identifying information about visitors to our site, we do use tracking technologies that can collect the following information about your visits on our site, including
Internet domain and IP address from which you access our website, the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the time and date you access your site, the pages you visit, and if you linked to our site from another website, the address of that website.
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors by learning about the number of visitors to our site, the types of technology our visitors use, and which pages and features are most popular. This information does not identify you personally, and we do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.
Release of Information to Third Parties
Script to Screen does not currently share any e-mail address you provide us , or personal information you specifically provide us with any other parties without your prior consent. Script to Screen may share aggregate data about our customers, traffic patterns, and other related site information with respectable third parties. None of this data is related to any individual’s name without their consent.
Off Site Links
Script to Screen is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any site that is linked to this one. Your activity on those sites is covered by the privacy policies on those sites.
Your Acceptance of Our Privacy Policy
By browsing or using this site, you signify your assent to the Script to Screen Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Script to Screen site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept the changes.
The Script to Screen Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time and without notice. This policy was last modified in February of 2018. Please check here for updates.
Pin It on Pinterest
Share This
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
LinkedIn
Make an Appointment
